

CONTACTS



+38 063 44 94 469



zadorozhniiV@gmail.com



<u>LinkedIn</u>



GitHub



Telegram

HARD SKILLS

- HTI M5
- **JavaScript**
- CSS3/SCSS/SASS
- Vue JS
- VueX
- Bootstrap / Vue Bootstrap
- Vuetify
- REST API, DOM API
- GitHub
- **ESLint / Prettier**

SOFT SKILLS

- Adaptability
- Flexibility
- Teamwork
- **Critical Observation**
- **Problem-Solving**
- **Fast Learning**

LANGUAGES

- Ukrainian native
- Russian native
- English Intermediate

EDUCATION

Front-End Development

Beetroot Academy

2022 May - 2022 September

Highest Education

Odessa National Maritime Academy

2009 - 2015

Hobby

Car traveling

Volodymyr Zadorozhnii

Front End Developer (Vue Is)

Specializations: Front-End Developer

Employment: full time

Work schedule: remote working, flexible schedule, full day

Location: Odessa, Ukraine

EXPERIENCE

Front-End Development Educations May 2022 -

Sept 2022 4 monthes

Development and creation of web projects. Layout of website and building with customization.

Proiects

- Game Store (HTML+ SCSS/SASS + Vue JS/VueX + Axios)
- Monticello (HTML+ SCSS/SASS +JQuery
- Pages book store (HTML+CSS + JS)
- BHROMAON (HTML+CSS only)

2020-2022 Second Officer | Su-Nav Management Navigation Officer / Watchkeeper

2 years

Took specific responsibility for navigation, the upkeep of charts, and software. Oversee navigation and radio equipment and undertake bridge watches at sea, was designated as safety and medical officer.

Responsibilities:

- Navigate the ship
- Respond to emergencies
- Safe and efficient voyage of the ship
- Route planning
- Chart and publication corrections
- Bridge equipment upkeep and maintenance
- Maintaining distress signaling equipment
- Control of the loading, stowage, securing and unloading of cargoes

2016-2020 Third Officer | Neptune Lines & Su-Nav Management

4 years

Safety Officer / Watchkeeper

Took special responsibilities to keep the ship, the people on board and the environment safe.

Responsibilities:

- Navigate the ship
- Upkeep of lifesaving and firefighting equipment
- Control of the loading, stowage, securing and unloading of cargoes
- Documents preparation for vessel arrive/departure in port

About Me

In past - seaman. Worked on Car and Bulk carriers. Carried a variety of goods (from timber and cars to electric windmill blades) to parts of the world (Nigeria to America and Canada), worked with many nationalities in fully mixed crews.

Now: I'm a hard-working and highly proficient Front-End Developer focused on web development, understanding of local development environments and integration of varying components. Ability to work efficiently independently with minimum supervision. I have creative thinking and high attention to detail. Can easily adapt to any technology required for

More than 10 years of experience in merchant shipping as an Officer formed in me a good understanding that persistence and stable work lead to good results.